The true death will come very soon
if you do not accept Lilith.
Lilith is a godless god.
She will lead you and all
around you to destruction.
- Alaska?
- I'll be there next week.
I want you to glamour me.
Make me forget about you.
- I want him gone, too.
- Goodbye, Hoyt.
Tonight, live from
New Orleans, Louisiana,
Reverend Steve Newlin.
He's in the state.
We have to go.
He probably left
for somewhere.
You know that Daddy doesn't
like it when you're human.
So what, then? You let Elijah take
everything from you?
We live in the wind
just like I did with Eric.
We're not running.
I lost Packmaster.
I've been abjured.
You're a lone wolf now,
just like your old man.
Lilith came to me
and she destroyed my maker
whom I was worshipping
as a false god.
We are the children
of Lilith.
You'll see that you and I
were meant to lead
our kind into the coming age.
What coming age?
The blood of the fae
allows us to daywalk.
We are of the night.
I can put you
back in the ground.
You can have your Lilith.
I will have the sun!
Where did you get this?
Underneath the floorboards
in my gran's house.
It's a contract
"I, John William Stackhouse
grant Mr. M. Warlow
my first fae-bearing
female heir."
Sookie.
Bill Compton.
Bill...
Compton.
Only one can lead us.
I choose you.
Drink the blood.
Drink it all.
No.
♪ True Blood 5x11♪
Sunset
Original Air Date on August 19, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ When you came in
the air went out ♪
♪ And every shadow
filled up with doubt ♪
♪ I don't know who
you think you are ♪
♪ But before
the night is through ♪
♪ I want to do
bad things with you ♪
♪ I'm the kind
to sit up in his room ♪
♪ Heart sick and eyes
filled up with blue ♪
♪ I don't know what
you've done to me ♪
♪ But I know
this much is true ♪
♪ I want to do
bad things with you ♪
♪ Ow, ooh ♪
♪ I want to do
real bad things with you. ♪
Lilith is a godless god.
She will lead you and all
around you to destruction.
If you kill and kill,
there will be nothing left,
not even you.
- No!
- Father!
General Cavanaugh
is coming.
Nora?
Yes?
We've received word
that General Cavanaugh
will be paying us a visit.
- Sorry.
- Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Something's different.
You've changed.
- Are you having doubts?
- No. No, of course not.
I'm worried about Russell.
His recklessness could destroy
everything we've worked for.
Russell's inconsequential.
He's nothing.
This is all part
of Lilith's plan.
Yes, of course.
We started this together,
you and I.
And now everything we've
dreamed of is coming to pass.
- The world will run with blood.
- Yes.
And we'll be there
to drink it down.
And in the darkness
we shall rejoice.
- I'll let the others know.
- Yeah. Go.
Jessica.
Hey, Bill. I was wondering
if I could use your phone.
- Mine doesn't work down here.
- For what purpose?
I've got to warn Jason.
When you were gone,
I had to stop Steve Newlin
from attacking him twice.
And now that Russell
and him are on the loose,
I'm really afraid
he's gonna do it again.
- So can I use it?
- I'm sorry, but no.
No?
But Jason is out there.
He's a sitting duck.
Sookie, too.
Jessica, it has taken me
a long while to come to terms
with the fact that part of
accepting the word of Lilith
into my heart has been
distancing myself
from the trivial
matters of humans.
It used to drive me crazy
worrying about their feelings
and their mortality
and their weakness
until I found
a better way--
Lilith's way.
And Jason and Sookie and
the inhabitants of Bon Temps
are no longer
our concern.
They are food
and nothing more.
You can't mean that.
You will see in time.
Now, I'm sorry,
but I have other matters
that I have to attend to.
But what if I made
him a vampire?
You want to be a maker?
I was--
I was reading
the Book of Lilith
and it says
that the greatest gift
you can give a human
is to make them a vampire.
That is true.
Well, that makes sense to me
because I love Jason,
but it never seems
to work out with him.
And I was thinking that's
probably because he's a human
and I'm a vampire.
But if I made him a vampire,
then we can be together.
You know, blessed
by Lilith.
Do you think
I'm an idiot?
What?
Are you really gonna stand there
and try and manipulate me
with your foolish lies?
- I'm not.
- Yes.
Please, can you send in
Gondry and Lambert?
What are you doing?
I'm taking you up
on your generous offer.
If you want to make
Jason Stackhouse into a vampire,
then by all means,
please do so.
No, Bill, I wasn't trying
to manipulate you.
No, no, no.
You're right.
In the time to come,
it may be important for me to
bolster the Compton bloodline.
So why not start right now?
As you rightly said,
as chancellor,
it would be hypocritical
of me to demand
that vampires
become makers
without requiring
the same thing of you.
- Wait, Bill.
- Gondry.
This is my progeny
Jessica.
I want you to take
her to Bon Temps
where she is gonna sire a young
man named Jason Stackhouse.
Take the helicopter.
I want this thing done properly.
- No, I don't need to, Bill.
- Don't let her out of your sight.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
What are we going to do?
I'll get us out of here.
You gonna be okay?
Kinda strange to find out
you were sold to a vampire
300 years ago.
Hey, that scroll thing
is bullshit.
I don't care what it says,
ain't nobody selling you.
Not on my watch.
I think he came for me.
- What are you talking about?
- Except he wasn't a vampire.
He was this weird air shape.
He said, "You are mine."
Well, that is...
really fucking creepy.
Maurella, she said talking
to this Elder person,
that could give us
some answers.
She said
it's worth a shot.
Oh, Sook.
Come here.
I've got to go.
Andy's got us doing triple shifts
with all these vamp attacks.
I'll come back tomorrow
and check up on you.
You stay here
where it's nice and safe.
Okay.
I just need your help
to get me out of here.
Oh.
Jason, promise me
you'll be careful.
Whoa.
Never gonna get
used to that.
Sir.
This way.
We'll be standing by
right here, sir.
Mm-hmm.
General Cavanaugh.
What a surprise.
So nice
to see you again.
Cut the crap,
Chancellor.
Where's Roman?
Unfortunately, the Guardian
is unavailable at this time.
Who the fuck are you?
General, this is
Chancellor Compton.
He's new.
Well, there's
a shit-storm out there
and Roman's been
ducking my calls.
Now I demand to know
what's going on.
Well, you're not in a position
to be making demands.
Oh, I see.
And who the fuck are you?
General Cavanaugh, we deeply
regret that Roman's not here,
but can we do anything
to help you?
We know you bombed
the Tru Blood factories.
That is absurd. Those factories
were bombed by terrorists.
Don't bullshit
a bullshitter, Rosalyn.
The US government and this
Authority have an arrangement.
The arrangement
is called mainstreaming.
It means you don't fuck with us,
we don't fuck with you.
Now, I've been working
with Roman to protect this
Authority for 20 years.
But this time
you've gone too far.
There are high-level talks
at the Pentagon right now
about how to eradicate vampires
from the face of the planet.
So I need to speak
with Roman.
Roman is no longer with us.
How?
He couldn't get with
the program, so he had to go.
This is a Sanguinist
regime now.
Lilith has guided us
to our rightful place,
and there we shall lead
all vampire-kind.
I would advise
you to be...
careful
about what words
you choose next.
You psychotic bloodsuckers.
Roman was the only one
keeping a lid on this.
He was the only one
stopping the world
from sliding back
into the Dark Ages.
Roman was an infidel
who defied the word of Lilith.
And now he's gone.
You strike me as a man of integrity,
General Cavanaugh.
Also a pragmatist.
Now this is the situation
that we find ourselves in.
You can join us or not.
I sincerely hope that you
choose the path forward.
We have video
of Russell Edgington
and Steve Newlin
eviscerating 22
fraternity brothers
at the local Gamma Kappa Tau
house last night.
There are copies of this.
If anything happens to me
now or in the future,
this is gonna be released
to the public.
You assured the world,
you assured the president
that Russell Edgington
was dead, and you lied.
So if that video
goes viral,
the human population is gonna
rise up against vampires
faster than you can say
"Molotov cocktail."
Your threats
are empty, General.
Are you really
that stupid?
We're prepared.
You don't think we've been planning
for this? We have weapons.
Weapons you have never
heard of.
We own the day.
Vampires don't stand
a fucking chance.
Now there's only one person
standing between you
and all-out war with the humans,
and you're looking at him.
So I suggest you think
very carefully
about what you say next.
That's what I thought.
Oh, God.
God is a vampire.
Oh, my.
Hi, Jason.
Jess.
What's going on?
Who are these guys?
Um...
Hey, guys,
you're kind of cramping my style.
Do you mind?
Your maker told me
to supervise,
so that's what I'm going to do--
supervise.
Okay.
Um...
Jason,
we've been through
a lot together,
and I think through
all of that, you know,
we've learned we can
trust each other.
I don't know about that.
It's kind of been
one of our issues.
- Just saying.
- Yeah, I know.
But I think you know
that you can trust me.
And I know
that I can trust you
to do the right thing.
Well, that's another thing--
we never do the right thing.
The right thing would be
not sleeping with each other
behind Hoyt's back.
You, me, we try
to be good people,
- but that don't mean that we are.
- Jason--
This is getting tiresome. We need
to get you two in the ground.
Let me do this.
If you don't do it,
I will.
What the hell
is he talking about?
Jess!
Fuck it.
Trust me.
No!
Oh, fuck!
You fucking idiot.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Do you have any idea
what you have done?
He was a dick.
I'm glad he killed
the bloated windbag.
They have weapons.
Now we're vulnerable.
- He was bluffing.
- You're all missing the point.
I'm just saying I have known
this rattlesnake.
- I knew his family.
- Shut up, Rosalyn!
- We need to clear this up.
- What do we do?
Listen!
I admit, I might have been
a bit impulsive here,
but I can fix this.
I'll go on
a glamouring campaign,
eliminate all memory
that the video exists.
It'll be like none
of this ever happened.
Yes, and I know
the general's chief of staff.
If we act quickly, we can
contain the situation.
Okay, go.
Take the AVL jet
and report back
when it is done.
Take a security detail.
Might need the backup.
Of course.
I'll handle
the general's entourage.
Baby, I am so sorry.
It's gonna be okay,
'cause you're gonna
wake up a vampire.
You shouldn't cry,
little girl.
This is a happy day.
When you and Prince Charming
wake tomorrow night,
he can bite you
right back.
Should we pick up some
takeout on our way back?
Do it.
- Fuck!
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I tried not to drink
too much of your blood.
Why?
Russell Edgington
and Steve Newlin,
they are coming for Sookie,
and Bill and Eric have gone
crazy on vampire religion
and nobody is gonna
save her this time.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Wait, Jason.
- What?
- I know this wasn't real.
But if I was gonna have to
spend eternity with somebody--
I mean...
I wasn't faking
that part.
I've got to go
warn Sookie.
We cleaned it all up.
There's not a drop
of Elijah anywhere.
I went over this place
with a toothbrush.
Killing a sheriff--
this is going to go up the chain.
- What chain?
- The fucking Authority.
What's the damn
Authority?
It's our government
and church combined.
The church runs
the government.
- Like the Vatican?
- Kind of.
They hand down the laws
and we follow them.
It's how it works.
Well, the Pope can fuck me
and so can the Authority.
They can both keep
their laws off of my body.
The Authority can do
whatever they want
with you and your body.
We're not going to talk
about this ever again.
- But do you think--
- For fuck's sake, Tara.
As your maker, I command
you to never speak
of Sheriff Stormer
and his untimely true death.
- Oh, hey.
- What the hell happened to you?
- I need you to hide me.
- No.
Why not?
Since when did I become
a halfway house
for wayward baby vamps?
Whatever trouble you're in,
leave me out of it.
I got enough of my own.
I know where Eric is.
- Where?
- I'll tell you if you hide me.
Don't play games with me,
you little ginger bitch.
Hide me.
Get her a coffin
out of storage.
Answers, now.
And despite what AVL
spokesperson Steve Newlin
said in his debate tonight,
local business
has dropped off 75%,
leading to worries that
dwindling supplies of Tru Blood
coupled with
the struggling economy...
You guys mind
if I change the station?
On Wall Street, the Dow
is down 200 points...
They'll be coming for us.
Dawn in two minutes.
Please retire to quarters.
Security protocols initiated.
Where the hell are we?
- I think we're underground.
- What is this place?
A fucking vampire
secret headquarters?
Emma's here somewhere.
Remember, it is truly
a great honor to meet the Elder.
Who is she, exactly?
She's the oldest fairy
to escape through the portal.
- There's only one problem.
- It's not a problem.
The Elder has been
through so many realms,
she's assumed so many shapes and
spoken so many languages
that she sometimes
has a difficult time...
- focusing.
- Focusing?
She operates on
many frequencies at once.
Time has
no meaning for her.
But you think
she can help me?
We shall see.
Your Grace.
This is Sookie Stackhouse,
the halfling
you were told about.
Ke$ha-- for or against?
Excuse me?
- Do you like her music?
- I'm sorry.
I'm not that familiar
with her music.
She doesn't really sing,
does she?
She talks.
I suppose that makes her
some sort of a poet.
That's alarming because
her spelling is atrocious.
Ha! Leave us.
Begging your pardon,
Miss Elder.
Maurella said that you might know
my great-great-great,
like, times 15 grandfather
John Stackhouse.
Johnny Stackhouse?
Yes, I did know him.
He was a landowner.
Very handsome.
Bit of a creep.
No offense.
None taken.
Do you know why he might
have promised me
to a vampire named Warlow?
It is forbidden to speak
of these things.
- What things?
- John Cougar Mellencamp, for or against?
Against.
What things?
Look, there is a reason
that you find
vampires irresistible,
a reason that you
slut your heart out
to every cute guy
out there with fangs.
- I beg your pardon?
- You, me, Warlow--
our destinies
are entwined.
Yes, okay, but what
is that supposed to mean?
A dark time is coming.
You will be tested.
Hold on to your light.
As long as we fairies
control our light,
we will be free.
Boyz II Men, for or against?
For. I'm sorry, I know you have
trouble with frequencies,
but there's a creepy
vampire ghost air monster
who killed my parents
and now he's coming to get me
and I really need you
to give me something concrete,
something useful.
My apologies.
There's so much information
in my head.
Eons of data.
Warlow is very--
Sookie!
Sook!
I've got to talk to you!
- Jason.
- Let me in!
- Where is she?
- He's been bitten.
We got to hide you
right now.
Oh, my God. What happened to you?
Are you okay?
Forget this. Russell Edgington
and Steve Newlin,
they're coming for you.
Bill, Eric, they've both gone crazy.
They found vampire religion,
so nobody's coming to save you.
Russell Edgington is alive?
- Yeah.
- Please, Miss Elder, you said Warlow is...?
Russell Edgington
is alive?
Hey there, sunshine.
Good morning,
Sheriff Bellefleur.
Egg sandwich,
crispy bacon,
large coffee,
extra milk, extra sugar.
You're so sweet, you make
the food here taste good.
I got a little
something else for you.
Come here.
My boys here
have something they want
to say to you.
Uh, hey,
Sheriff Bellefleur.
Uh, I just want to say
that I'm sorry
for putting your butt
up on Facebook.
Uh, it was wrong
and it seems like you're
making my mom real happy.
You know, way happier
than my pops ever did.
So, sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
Sorry that I cannot scrape
the image of your ass
- from the back wall of my mind.
- Rocky.
Sorry I'm gonna have to waste all
of my mama's hard-earned tips
to pay for years of therapy and
probably end up incarcerated anyway.
Rocky Cleary, you quit
your sass right now.
You can't make me say
stuff that I don't feel.
It's all right, Holly.
He's got no reason
to trust me.
Yet.
But I'm gonna make
you boys a promise.
I am gonna do right
by your mama
for as long
as she'll have me.
You can take that
to the bank.
Banks suck.
They took our house.
It's a figure
of speech, son.
What do you say?
Come on.
All right.
No, that's all right.
Okay.
All righty, then.
I'll see you at lunch.
Jackson.
Alcide, look at you.
Ain't seen you
since you was a pup.
Mr. Rollins.
What do you want?
Just out warning folks.
There's been a bunch
of baby vamp attacks
in Madison
and Rankin Counties.
Kills are messy, savage.
We think the vamps
are upping their numbers,
turning folks,
letting them run wild.
Baby vamps are forming
into packs, hunting.
Coming our way.
Silver-plated
box fence.
Won't stop
the grown vamps,
but it'll keep
the baby ones out.
Get off my land.
Good to see you're still
a son of a bitch, Herveaux.
I come out here
out of respect
for a man I once knew.
No good deed goes
unpunished, I guess.
You were a Packmaster,
but you threw it all away.
I was forced out
by you turncoats.
Don't let your old man
drag you down, Alcide.
He's quicksand.
Rollins is a lying shit.
Comes out here acting
all high and mighty.
He can go to hell.
Can't trust him,
that's the truth.
You did it.
So why don't we just stop
pretending like you didn't?
You stole that money
from the pack.
That's why
they kicked you out.
And there ain't a damn thing
you can do to change that.
I don't need Rollins
coming out here
digging up
ancient history.
And I sure as hell
don't need my kid
passing judgment.
You get it?
Whatever happened
to pack first?
Pack left me
out here to rot.
Pack can go
fuck themselves.
Listen to me!
Russell Edgington is gonna
keep coming for me.
He's not gonna stop.
And after he's gotten me,
he's gonna come for you.
Now, I don't know about you guys,
but I am tired of running.
We have to fight him,
all of us together.
I'm sorry.
It's suicide.
And yet we must.
We, the fairy tribe
of Bon Temps,
in this plane,
in this time,
will fight with you,
Sookie Stackhouse.
You clear on the plan?
Just be honest.
Tell the truth.
No, I won't have
to tell the truth.
- 'Cause I'm gonna kill him.
- You don't have to do that.
You could just
stay here with me.
No, I want to do it.
Sook, if there's
one thing I learned
from my time as QB-1,
it's that the best defense
is a good offense.
So no more pussyfooting
around Russell.
It's game time.
I love you.
I love you, too, Sook.
You give him hell.
I always do.
Hey, y'all.
Here you go.
- Come here.
- Oh!
Terry Bellefleur, you're gonna get
me in trouble.
Sam's not even around.
Yeah, but Lafayette
is a snitch.
I'm a bitch,
not a snitch.
Love it.
I'm so glad to see
y'all back and happy
and, you know,
in love and all.
Thank you, cuz.
I appreciate that.
She saves my life
every day.
How do you make it last
for the long haul?
Well...
I think it starts
with trust.
- Trust most of all.
- Yeah.
And honesty.
Got to have honesty.
- Yeah, that, too.
- And loyalty.
You got to know that person's
gonna be there for you
through thick and thin
'cause you never know
when some Iraqi ghost lady
is gonna curse
your entire family.
There you are.
Maurella,
what are you doing here?
There's danger
afoot, Andrew.
You swore on the light
to protect me
and the fruit of our union.
Andy Bellefleur!
Did you put that bun
in her oven?
But I just saw you
about a week ago,
and you weren't pregnant.
That was the night
we conceived.
One week ago,
and now you're...
Yes.
Right on schedule.
Look, Maurella, you seem
like a lovely person.
Mmm, I am.
- And I know that we have--
- Twice.
But I'm not stupid.
A lot of people might think I'm stupid,
but those people are wrong.
No, I don't think
you're stupid.
Well, apparently you do
if you think you can
pull this over on me.
Did you or did you not
swear upon the light?
All I know is your finger
lit up and I touched it.
You accepted
my light into you.
Otherwise I never would
have shared flesh with you.
Twice.
But I can't--
I got a good thing
starting with Holly.
And I just feel
more comfortable
with somebody
who's the same species.
To ignore the light pact
will bring great dishonor
upon me and all my clan.
It is an act of war.
Bill-- I've never
seen him like that.
He was cold, cruel even.
That's nest behavior.
When vampires live together
for a long time
and feed off
of each other's blood,
they form a nest
and become sadistic
and crazy.
From what you're telling me,
drinking that Lilith's blood
is making them
into a nest on steroids.
Have you ever been
in a nest?
Eric and I have
steered clear.
I find most vampires
as irritating as most humans.
Are you worried about Eric?
He's a big boy.
He can take care of himself.
Well, thank you again
for letting me stay here.
Totally. Maybe later we can braid
each other's hair
and talk about boys.
Fucking baby vamps.
She's all bark,
isn't she?
Nah, she's a lot
of bark
and a lot of bite.
Do you like her?
What?
You know, like...
like, like her.
No.
Why would you even
say something like that?
I'm just asking.
I don't know that many people of
the gay persuasion.
It just looked like maybe you two
were getting along.
I'm sorry, but you have no idea
what you're talking about.
I didn't say that I did.
That's why I was asking.
Pam and me--
never gonna happen.
Okay. Fine.
Sorry I asked.
Why you feel the need to get
all up in my business?
'Cause I don't have
any friends.
I don't have anyone
to talk to.
And even if you
freak out
and go crazy now and again
and beat me up,
I'm a vampire now,
so I heal.
And I like
talking to you.
I'll try and bring you
a fangbanger later.
Thanks.
We're all out
of Tru Blood.
What else you serving?
You're welcome to try
your luck with this fine
cross section of humanity.
I'm looking for someone.
My progeny.
He's sheriff of these parts.
Came by here last night.
We paid our taxes
and he moved on.
- Oh, is that right?
- Yeah.
Ah!
I can smell
Elijah's blood on you.
A maker always knows
when her progeny dies.
He was only one
of 204,
but it's still like
a cold spike in your heart.
Who killed him?
Was it you?
It was me.
What possessed you
to murder my progeny?
He was getting
on my nerves.
In the name of the one
true Vampire Authority,
in whose wisdom and justice
all is made manifest by Lilith,
I arrest you for the murder
of Sheriff Elijah Stormer.
Your daddy
is looking for you.
Bill Compton.
Only one can lead us.
I choose you.
I'm not worthy.
Drink of me.
Drink all of me.
He's all over the guy.
He's hanging all over the fucking guy,
you blind prick!
Whoo-hoo!
- Yeah.
- Ah! Fuckin' A!
Fuckin' A.
I'm healing.
- Don't go out there.
- Ah! Ah!
They're heading over
to the Reeves place.
You always got to be
the fuckin' hero.
You raised me to be
a man and a wolf,
not a thief and a coward.
Jesus!
I actually met him.
He was a boring hippie
who stank of patchouli.
Hi, Jason.
Oh, look.
We got ourselves
a hunk sandwich.
Get your fucking
hands off me.
- Get off me!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Where's your sister?
Yeah, you ain't never
gonna find her.
'Cause she's someplace
you can't get in.
And where might that be?
She's with the fairies.
What fairies?
There's a bunch of them.
They got a club
out by the Thibodeaux Farm.
How about you lead us to
this spritely smorgasbord?
Okay.
Stay just like that
until we find her.
Oh, you bet.
Who knows how to
show you a good time?
You do.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Come out here!
- We're not gonna hurt ya.
- We're just gonna eat ya.
- Let's flip this fucker.
- Leave her be!
When we die, we're goo?
You're already dead.
Twist his head off!
Motherfucker.
No!
- Emma?
- Oh, shit.
What the fuck
kind of monsters are you?
Oh, my God.
Hey there, baby.
You're fine.
Just don't shift.
We have to hurry.
What the fuck are you
doing out?
- Shift.
- I'm not gonna leave her.
We won't.
Chancellor Compton
is requesting his breakfast.
Hey, wait.
I'll go.
That's a first.
You in a hurry to die?
Just as soon
get it over with.
Do whatever you have to!
Sam!
Chancellor?
Lilith came to me.
She chose me.
No.
She chose me!
Take her to the cells.
Chelsea, will you please
page Chancellor Compton?
What the fuck
are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
Hey, help Luna!
Who the fuck is Luna?
Fuck you!
Chancellor Compton,
your progeny will meet you
in the main chamber.
What do you have
to say for yourself?
I'm sorry.
I just--
when I got there,
Jason wasn't into it.
I didn't think
it was right.
So you decided it would be better
to kill two vampires instead?
That security guy,
he was gonna make me turn him.
He was doing his job--
following my orders.
You chose a human
over two vampires.
He's not a human.
He's Jason.
You staked Longshadow
for Sookie.
Lilith commands that vampire
hath dominion over human.
Who cares about Lilith?
Pam says you are in a nest
and it is making you crazy.
Who are you
to defy me?
I am the chosen one!
Lilith chose me!
Only one can lead us.
I choose you.
Drink of me.
Drink all of me.
Baby, let me out.
Baby, open the door.
What is that smell?
Fairy.
Where are they?
Right there.
Where?
There.
- That smell.
- Where are they?
I can feel them.
They're all around me.
What fucking
fairy magic is this?
Where are they?
Oh, mercy!
- What are you waiting for?
- We're ready to fight.
Jason brought them here.
That was the plan.
The plan has changed.
Where are you, fairy?
Sookie Stackhouse,
I will tear your brother
limb from limb unless
you show yourself.
We have to fight them.
I'm not letting you out there
to get yourselves killed.
- You said we were--
- Don't worry. I got this.
Sookie Stackhouse!
Oh...
As I live and breathe.
A fairy.
Ah!
Impressive.
You are turbocharged.
Vampire, I hereby banish you
to the realms and beyond.
Begone!
Jason!
Jason.
I said begone.
Oh, sweet
merciful fuck!
That was delicious!
Heaven, thy name
is fairy.
Oh, God.
He can see us.
Why, thank you so much.
I'd love to come
to dinner.
- ♪ Sunset ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ Whoa oh ♪
- ♪ Sunset ♪
- ♪ It's sunset ♪
♪ Sunset ♪
- ♪ Sunset ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ Sunset ♪
♪ Whoa oh ♪
- ♪ Sunset ♪
- ♪ It's sunset ♪
♪ Sunset ♪
♪ You went and left me ♪
♪ Here all alone ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ You turned
and walked away ♪
♪ About this time
one day ♪
- ♪ Sunset ♪
- ♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Sunset ♪
♪ Whoa oh... ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net